trivia_db = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Celiac Disease is a disease that effects the heart, causing those effected to be unable to eat meat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Steel is an alloy of Iron and Carbon.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The chemical element Lithium is named after the country of Lithuania.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Shrimp can swim backwards.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The &quot;Gympie Stinger&quot; is the deadliest plant in the world.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
